TAP version 13
# Subtest: clampBox leaves a box that already fits untouched
ok 1 - clampBox leaves a box that already fits untouched
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.4794
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: clampBox pulls a box back inside the container on the right/bottom
ok 2 - clampBox pulls a box back inside the container on the right/bottom
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1406
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: clampBox pulls a box back inside on negative x/y
ok 3 - clampBox pulls a box back inside on negative x/y
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.8921
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: clampBox shrinks a box larger than the container
ok 4 - clampBox shrinks a box larger than the container
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6583
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: clampBox enforces a minimum size
ok 5 - clampBox enforces a minimum size
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6933
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: applyAspectRatio with ratio 0 (free-form) just clamps
ok 6 - applyAspectRatio with ratio 0 (free-form) just clamps
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8734
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: applyAspectRatio produces the requested width/height ratio
ok 7 - applyAspectRatio produces the requested width/height ratio
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3927
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: applyAspectRatio keeps the box centered on the same point when possible
ok 8 - applyAspectRatio keeps the box centered on the same point when possible
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0318
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: applyAspectRatio never produces a box larger than the container
ok 9 - applyAspectRatio never produces a box larger than the container
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.8408
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: defaultBox is centered, inset from the edges, and matches the given ratio
ok 10 - defaultBox is centered, inset from the edges, and matches the given ratio
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3312
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: computeOutputSize leaves a small box unscaled
ok 11 - computeOutputSize leaves a small box unscaled
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7759
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: computeOutputSize downscales a box larger than maxDim, preserving aspect ratio
ok 12 - computeOutputSize downscales a box larger than maxDim, preserving aspect ratio
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.5088
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: computeOutputSize never upscales
ok 13 - computeOutputSize never upscales
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0611
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: computeOutputSize always returns at least 1x1
ok 14 - computeOutputSize always returns at least 1x1
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8008
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..14
# tests 14
# suites 0
# pass 14
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 514.5495
